

NGUYỄN TRẦN ĐĂNG KHOA DEVELOPER

PROFILE

With a passion for programming, I want to get a position where I can devote myself to the company and at the same time gain more experience for myself. I am very serious at work. I am willing to switch technology according to the company's requirements.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

Programming languages: HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, Java (JSP, SERVLET), C.

Library & framework: BOOSTRAP, JQUERY, VUE JS, ANGULAR, EXPRESS JS, SPRING BOOT, QUARKUS.

Database: SQL server, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB.

Foreign language: English (B1) Order: GitHub, GitLab, Docker, Jenkins, Keycloak, SonarQube,

Harbor, Nginx.

CONTACT

Telephone: 0843152505

Email: Khoab1910240@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

DORMITORY MANAGEMENT PROJECT

08/2022 - 12/2022

This is a website project to help people easily manage student dormitory. (HTML, CSS, JS, JQUERY, PHP & MYSQL).

https://github.com/DangKhoaB1910240/DormitoryManagement.gi

DRINKS ORDER PROJECT

12/2022 - 01/2023

Website makes it easy for people to order drinks. (HTML, CSS, JS, JQUERY, PHP & MYSQL).

https://github.com/DangKhoaB1910240/Drinks.git

WATCH STORE PROJECT

02/2023 - 03/2023

Website makes it easy for people to sell watch. (Node, Vue JS, MongoDB).

https://github.com/DangKhoaB1910240/WatchStore.git

SEAT RESERVATION (2 months internship at Axon active company)

05/2023 – 07/2023

This website is written exclusively for Axon active company. It is used to be able to manage the seat reservation efficiently (Quarkus, Keycloak, Angular, Docker, Jenkins, SonarQube, PostgreSQL).

EDUCATION

CAN THO UNIVERSITY (08/2019 - 12/2023)

Major: Information technology

GPA: 3.56/4

COMMUNICATION

High teamwork spirit, good communication and I used to work with Scrum.